[{
    "question": "`9*1`",
    "answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`10*5`",
    "answer": "`50`"
},
{
    "question": "`4*5`",
    "answer": "`20`"
},
{
    "question": "`7*5`",
    "answer": "`35`"
},
{
    "question": "`5*4`",
    "answer": "`20`"
},
{
    "question": "`9*11`",
    "answer": "`99`"
},
{
    "question": "`3*10`",
    "answer": "`30`"
},
{
    "question": "`11*9`",
    "answer": "`99`"
},
{
    "question": "`6*6`",
    "answer": "`36`"
},
{
    "question": "`5*7`",
    "answer": "`35`"
},
{
    "question": "`10*10`",
    "answer": "`100`"
},
{
    "question": "`0*9`",
    "answer": "`0`"
},
{
    "question": "`9*11`",
    "answer": "`99`"
},
{
    "question": "`11*5`",
    "answer": "`55`"
},
{
    "question": "`9*6`",
    "answer": "`54`"
},
{
    "question": "`3*3`",
    "answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`8*7`",
    "answer": "`56`"
},
{
    "question": "`8*5`",
    "answer": "`40`"
},
{
    "question": "`5*4`",
    "answer": "`20`"
},
{
    "question": "`2*3`",
    "answer": "`6`"
}]